<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Best Pickup Lines 2023</string>
    <string name="line">

"Did it hurt when you fell from heaven?"\n\n
        "Can I buy you a drink?"\n\n

"You must be tired, because you've been running through my mind all day."\n\n

"Are you a magician? Because whenever I look at you, everyone else disappears."\n\n

"Is your name Wi-Fi? Because I'm really feeling a connection."\n\n

"Do you believe in love at first sight, or should I walk by again?"\n\n

"Are you a beaver? Because daaaaaaaaam!"\n\n

"Is your name Google? Because you've got everything I've been searching for."\n\n

"Are you a library book? Because I can't stop checking you out."\n\n

"Do you have a map? Because I just got lost in your eyes."\n\n

"Are you a parking ticket? Because you've got FINE written all over you."\n\n

"Is your name Ariel? Because we were mermaid for each other."\n\n

"Are you a camera? Because every time I look at you, I smile."\n\n

"Are you a thief? Because you just stole my heart."\n\n

"Do you have a Band-Aid? Because I just scraped my knee falling for you."\n\n

"Are you a time traveler? Because I can't imagine my future without you."\n\n

"Are you a scientist? Because I feel like I'm in a lab, and you're my perfect experiment."\n\n

"Are you a chef? Because you just spiced up my life."\n\n

"Do you have a name or can I call you mine?"\n\n

"Are you an alien? Because your beauty is out of this world."\n\n

"Do you have a boyfriend/girlfriend, or can I be your girlfriend/boyfriend?"\n\n

"Is your dad a thief? Because he stole the stars and put them in your eyes."\n\n

"Do you have a twin sister/brother? Because I've been seeing double all night."\n\n

"Do you have a Band-Aid? Because I just hurt myself falling for you."\n\n

"Are you a bank loan? Because you have my interest."\n\n

"Are you a magician? Because you just made my heart disappear."\n\n

"Is your name Summer? Because you're hot."\n\n

"Is your name Apple? Because you're the apple of my eye."\n\n

"Is your name Honey? Because you're so sweet."\n\n

"Are you a teacher? Because you're teaching me how to fall in love."\n\n

"Do you have a license? Because you're driving me crazy."\n\n

"Are you a rocket scientist? Because you're out of this world."\n\n

"Is your name Cinderella? Because I think we're a perfect fit."\n\n

"Is your name Angel? Because you've got wings."\n\n

"Are you a genie? Because you've granted my wish."\n\n

"Is your name Barbie? Because you're beautiful and perfect."\n\n

"Do you work at a bakery? Because you've got a nice set of buns."\n\n

"Is your name Rapunzel? Because I'm stuck in your hair."\n\n

"Are you a birdwatcher? Because you're the only bird I want to watch."\n\n

"Do you have a name, or can I call you mine?"\n\n

"Is your name Winter? Because you're making my heart melt."\n\n

"Excuse me, do you have a name or can I call you mine?"\n\n

"Do you have a map? I just got lost in your eyes."\n\n

"Are you a magician? Every time I look at you, everyone else disappears."\n\n

"Do you have a Band-Aid? I just scraped my knee falling for you."\n\n

"Do you believe in love at first sight or should I walk by again?"\n\n

"Are you a time traveler? Because I see you in my future."\n\n

"Can I follow you home? Because my parents always told me to follow my dreams."\n\n

"If you were a library book, I'd never return you because you're overdue for a date."\n\n

"Do you have a sunburn or are you always this hot?"\n\n

"Are you a beaver? Because daaaaamn, you're fine."\n\n

"Is it just me, or do we have some kind of chemistry here?"\n\n

"Do you have a personality or can I be your sole source of happiness?"\n\n

"If you were a booger, I'd pick you first."\n\n

"Are you a thief? Because you just stole my heart."\n\n

"Can I borrow a quarter? I want to call my mom and tell her I just met the man/woman of my dreams."\n\n

"Are you a pirate? Because I think I found my treasure."\n\n

"Can I take a picture of you so I can show Santa what I want for Christmas?"\n\n

"Are you a genie? Because you just granted my wish of finding someone as amazing as you."\n\n

"Excuse me, can you hold this for a second? I need to tie my shoe…and my heartstrings because you've got me trippin'."\n\n

"Can I have your picture so I can show Santa what I want for Christmas?"\n\n

"Is your name Google? Because you have everything I've been searching for."\n\n

"Are you an alien? Because your beauty is out of this world."\n\n

"Do you have a magnet in your pocket? Because I'm attracted to you."\n\n

"Do you have a map to your heart? Because I'm lost in your eyes."\n\n

"Can I borrow a kiss? I promise I'll give it back."\n\n

"If you were a vegetable, you'd be a cutecumber."\n\n

"Do you have a phone? I need to call Heaven because I've found an angel."\n\n

"Are you an interior decorator? Because when I saw you, the entire room became beautiful."\n\n

"Do you have a Band-Aid? Because I just scraped my knee falling for you."\n\n

"Is your name Ariel? Because we mermaid for each other."\n\n

"Are you a camera? Because every time I look at you, I smile."\n\n

"Do you have a twin sister/brother? Because I've been seeing double all night."\n\n

"Can I borrow a map? Because I just got lost in your eyes."\n\n

"Is it hot in here, or is it just you?"\n\n

"Are you a parking ticket? Because you've got 'fine' written all over you."\n\n

"Can I tie your shoes? Because I can't have you falling for anyone else."\n\n

"Do you have a library card? Because I'm checking you out."\n\n

"Are you a magician? Because every time I look at you, everyone else disappears."\n\n

"Do you have a sunburn or are you always this hot?"\n\n

"Is your name Wi-Fi? Because I'm really feeling a connection."\n\n

"Excuse me, do you have a name or can I call you mine?"\n\n

"If you were a vegetable, you'd be a cutecumber."\n\n

"Are you a camera? Because every time I look at you, I smile."\n\n

"Are you a camera? Because every time I look at you, I smile," said the smooth talker.\n\n

"Do you have a name? Or can I call you mine?" asked the charming individual.\n\n

"I hope you know CPR because you are taking my breath away," said the person with a twinkle in their eye.\n\n

"Are you a time traveler? Because I see you in my future," said the romantic optimist.\n\n

"If you were words on a page, you'd be the fine print," said the clever wordsmith.\n\n

"You must be a magician. Because any time I look at you, everyone else disappears," said the person with a hint of admiration.\n\n

"Your hand looks heavy. Can I hold it for you?" asked the courteous person.\n\n

"Your lips look lonely. Would they like to meet mine?" asked the cheeky charmer.\n\n

"I'm not currently an organ donor, but I'd love to give you my heart," said the person with a bold declaration.\n\n

"You can delete the app now, I'm here," said the confident person.\n\n

"I'd take you to the movies, but they don't let you bring in your own snacks," said the playful flirt.\n\n

"Hey, how was heaven when you left it?" asked the person with a flirty smile.\n\n

"I bet you dinner that you won’t give me your number."\n\n

"How can I plan our wedding without having your number?"\n\n

"What number should I send my good morning texts to?"\n\n

"I’m writing a phone book, can I get your number?"\n\n

"Can I borrow your phone? I need to call God and tell him I’ve found his missing angel."\n\n

"My phone’s broken, it doesn’t have your number in it."\n\n

"I’m no mathematician, but I’m pretty good with numbers. Tell you what, give me yours and watch what I can do with it."\n\n

"I think there’s something wrong with my phone. Could you call it and see if it works?"\n\n

"When I text you goodnight later, what phone number should I use?"\n\n

"I bet my number sounds nicer than yours. Wanna hear it?"\n\n

"I think your number will be safer in my phone than in your head."\n\n

"I seem to have lost my phone number. Can I have yours?"\n\n

    </string>

</resources>